{
    "id": "d0237bad35994db1a71bc71e1a11c7ec",
    "title": "Prepositions Of Movement",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "I don’t know how I managed to get ………………… this mess.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "into",
                "on to",
                "to"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "38e88118175c4d159572edebd14a01b7"
        },
        {
            "question": "I hope you won’t run …………………. any problems.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "on to",
                "into"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "50910ba7fb25438daf4724879dbd0e06"
        },
        {
            "question": "He was trying to throw his hat ……………….. the roof.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "into",
                "on to"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "97160c2030f542dc9d4f3cd7eef41e45"
        },
        {
            "question": "John always manages to get ……………… trouble.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "on to",
                "into"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "8b6952606f794c07b2cbc7dce07affe0"
        },
        {
            "question": "He threw himself …………………. the work with great enthusiasm.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "at",
                "into",
                "on to"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "67295ca358284333b51bd473d1d6fccb"
        },
        {
            "question": "She ran ………………….. the room.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "out",
                "out of",
                "of"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "ff60de7adc244fb7a0bbff6e4d414b9d"
        },
        {
            "question": "I took the envelope …………………. my pocket.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "out",
                "out from",
                "out of"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "f75586580a2e458fac8f5492c575cebe"
        },
        {
            "question": "She sat there staring ………………….. the window.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "on to",
                "on",
                "out of"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "410132b52a0549a4b755c97898ee4f74"
        },
        {
            "question": "John wants to get ………………… advertising.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "at",
                "in",
                "into"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "202479f75a0347ac976f959cc75a3c4d"
        },
        {
            "question": "He promised that he would look ………………….. the matter.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "at",
                "on to",
                "into"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "cd736ecdd5264ac98e7dddc4aae89cfc"
        }
    ]
}